Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
1889-2009
1889 2009
North Carolina State University Media Relations
UA 015.010
The North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records contain materials related to nearly every sport that has been played at the university, including sports that are no longer active. Types of materials include: press releases, game/event programs, schedules, rosters, clippings, correspondence, brochures, scoring sheets and other game/event notes, photographs, and a variety of other general information documenting the activities of each sport. Materials range in date from 1889 to 2009.
Athletics officially began at the North Carolina College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts (later, North Carolina State University) on March 2, 1892, when a football team made up of students at the college defeated a team from the Raleigh Male Academy. After the college's Board of Trustees made the decision to grant the team requested funds in 1893, North Carolina A&M played its first formal (non-scrimmage) intercollegiate game that fall against the University of North Carolina's football second team. In 1921, NC State became a charter member of the Southern Intercollegiate Conference, remaining until 1953, when along with Duke, UNC-Chapel Hill, Maryland, South Carolina, Wake Forest, and Clemson, the university withdrew to form the Atlantic Coast Conference. In 1974, the first women's athletic teams began play. As of 2009, NC State had eleven men's and eleven women's varsity athletic teams in the Atlantic Coast Conference. The Media Relations office (formerly, Sports Information) has existed in some form at NC State since the 1940s, as a reference and records-keeping center for statistics and information relating to NC State Athletics.
233 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Transferred from North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations.
The records of North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations are arranged into the following series (28): News Releases, General Records, Baseball, Men's Basketball, Women's Basketball, Men's Cross Country, Men's Fencing, Football, Men's Golf, Men's Gymnastics, Men's Lacrosse, Men's Rifle, Men's Soccer, Men's Swimming and Diving, Men's Tennis, Men's Track and Field, Wrestling, Women's Gymnastics, Softball, Women's Swimming and Diving, Women's Soccer, Women's Cross Country, Women's Tennis, Women's Track and Field, Women's Fencing, Women's Golf, Volleyball, and Cheerleading. Within each series, materials are arranged chronologically by season, with season-long and general information files preceding files from individual events during that season (where present).
Athletics began officially at the North Carolina College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts (later renamed North Carolina State University) in 1892 when a group of student formed a football team to play against a local high school. The following year it played its first formal games after the Board of Trustees granted it funds. The baseball team first played in 1894, and men’s basketball in 1911. In the early years the teams used various nicknames, including "Red Terrors." In 1921, the NC State football team began using the name "Wolfpack," and in 1947 this name was officially adopted for all athletic teams. NC State became a charter member of the Southern Conference in 1921, but it left in 1953 to help form the Atlantic Coast Conference. The racial integration of athletics began at NC State in 1958. In 1974, the first women's athletic team (basketball) began play, and the following year women's softball and volleyball were introduced.
For more information on the history of particular sports, see the notes for each one listed on the "Contents" tab.
The North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records contain materials related to nearly every sport played at the university, including sports that are no longer active. Types of materials include: press releases, game/event programs, schedules, rosters, clippings, correspondence, brochures, scoring sheets and other game/event notes, photographs, and a variety of other general information documenting the activities of each sport. Materials range in date from 1889 to 2009.
North Carolina State College--History; Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women; North Carolina College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts--History; Sloan Norman 1926-; Case Everett N. Everett Norris 1900-1966; Atlantic Coast Conference; Esposito Sam; Yow Kay 1942-2009; Valvano Jim; Weedon J. Franklin; North Carolina State University Media Relations; Southern Intercollegiate Conference; Southern Conference; National Collegiate Athletic Association; North Carolina State University Media Relations; North Carolina Diving; North Carolina Diving for women; North Carolina Track and field; North Carolina Tennis; North Carolina Soccer; North Carolina Soccer for women; North Carolina Swimming; North Carolina Swimming for women; North Carolina Athletics; North Carolina Coaches (Athletics); North Carolina Rifle practice; North Carolina Lacrosse; North Carolina Baseball; Basketball coaches; North Carolina College athletes; North Carolina Women athletes; North Carolina Fencing; North Carolina Cross-country running; North Carolina Basketball; North Carolina Basketball for women; North Carolina Volleyball; North Carolina Gymnastics; North Carolina Golf; North Carolina Golf for women; Sports records; North Carolina Raleigh Sports facilities; North Carolina History 20th century College sports; North Carolina Cheerleading; North Carolina Wrestling; North Carolina Softball
- News Releases, 1955-1997; 1955 1997
  This series contains press and news releases distributed by the Media Relations (formerlly, Sports Information) office covering all university sports, though the majority of the releases cover men's basketball and football. Some duplication of these releases exists in this collection; duplicate releases can be found in the series of the sport they pertain to. Materials are arranged roughly in chronological order. The file of undated releases at the end of this series are from some time prior to 1960; a more exact date cannot be determined.
  - Sports shorts and fillers, 1955 (Legalbox 12, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, 1957-1959 (Legalbox 1, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Jun. 1960 - Feb. 1961 (Legalbox 1, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Mar. 1961 - Feb. 1962 (Legalbox 1, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Jul. 1962 (Legalbox 1, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Nov. 1962 (Legalbox 1, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1962 - Mar. 1963 (Legalbox 1, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Mar. - May 1963 (Legalbox 1, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Dec. 1963 (Legalbox 1, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1963 - Mar. 1964 (Legalbox 2, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Aug. 1964 (Legalbox 2, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Nov. 1964 (Legalbox 2, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1964 - Mar. 1965 (Legalbox 2, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Jun. 1965 (Legalbox 2, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Nov. 1965 (Legalbox 2, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1965 - May 1966 (Legalbox 2, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Nov. 1966 (Legalbox 2, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1966 - Mar. 1967 (Legalbox 3, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Jun. 1967 (Legalbox 3, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Jun. - Nov. 1967 (Legalbox 3, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1967 - Feb. 1968 (Legalbox 3, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Mar. - May 1968 (Legalbox 3, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Dec. 1968 (Legalbox 3, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Dec. 1968 - Apr. 1969 (Legalbox 3, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Jul. 1969 (Legalbox 3, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Nov. 1969 (Legalbox 4, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Dec. 1969 - Mar. 1970 (Legalbox 4, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Jun. 1970 (Legalbox 4, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Dec. 1970 (Legalbox 4, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1970 - Mar. 1971 (Legalbox 4, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Nov. 1971 (Legalbox 4, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1971 - Mar. 1972 (Legalbox 5, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Jun. 1972 (Legalbox 5, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Oct. 1972 (Legalbox 5, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1972 - Feb. 1973 (Legalbox 5, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Sept. 1973 (Legalbox 5, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Oct. 1973 - Jan. 1974 (Legalbox 5, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Feb. - Sept. 1974 (Legalbox 6, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Oct. 1974 - Mar. 1975 (Legalbox 6, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Apr. - Sept. 1975 (Legalbox 6, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1975 - Feb. 1976 (Legalbox 6, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Oct. 1976 (Legalbox 6, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Nov. 1976 - Feb. 1977 (Legalbox 7, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1977 (Legalbox 7, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1977 (Legalbox 7, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1977 (Legalbox 7, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1977 (Legalbox 7, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1978 (Legalbox 7, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1978 (Legalbox 7, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, May - Jun. 1978 (Legalbox 7, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1978 (Legalbox 7, Folder 9)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1978 (Legalbox 7, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1978 (Legalbox 7, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1979 (Legalbox 7, Folder 12)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1979 (Legalbox 7, Folder 13)
  - Press releases, May - Jun. 1979 (Legalbox 8, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1979 (Legalbox 8, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1979 (Legalbox 8, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1979 (Legalbox 8, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1980 (Legalbox 8, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1980 (Legalbox 8, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, May - Jun. 1980 (Legalbox 8, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1980 (Legalbox 8, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1980 (Legalbox 8, Folder 9)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1980 (Legalbox 8, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1981 (Legalbox 8, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1981 (Legalbox 8, Folder 12)
  - Press releases, May - Jun. 1981 (Legalbox 8, Folder 13)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1981 (Legalbox 8, Folder 14)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1981 (Legalbox 8, Folder 15)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1981 (Legalbox 8, Folder 16)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1982 (Legalbox 9, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1982 (Legalbox 9, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1982 (Legalbox 9, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1982 (Legalbox 9, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1982 (Legalbox 9, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1983 (Legalbox 9, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1983 (Legalbox 9, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, May - Jun. 1983 (Legalbox 9, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1983 (Legalbox 9, Folder 9)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1983 (Legalbox 9, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1983 (Legalbox 9, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1984 (Legalbox 9, Folder 12)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1984 (Legalbox 9, Folder 13)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1984 (Legalbox 9, Folder 14)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1984 (Legalbox 9, Folder 15)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1984 (Legalbox 9, Folder 16)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1985 (Legalbox 10, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1985 (Legalbox 10, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1985 (Legalbox 10, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1985 (Legalbox 10, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1985 (Legalbox 10, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1986 (Legalbox 10, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1986 (Legalbox 10, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, Jul - Aug. 1986 (Legalbox 10, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1986 (Legalbox 10, Folder 9)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1986 (Legalbox 10, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1987 (Legalbox 10, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1987 (Legalbox 10, Folder 12)
  - Press releases, May - Jun. 1987 (Legalbox 10, Folder 13)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1987 (Legalbox 10, Folder 14)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1987 (Legalbox 10, Folder 15)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1987 (Legalbox 10, Folder 16)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1988 (Legalbox 10, Folder 17)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Apr. 1988 (Legalbox 10, Folder 18)
  - Press releases, May - Jun. 1988 (Legalbox 10, Folder 19)
  - Press releases, Jul. - Aug. 1988 (Legalbox 10, Folder 20)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Oct. 1988 (Legalbox 11, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1988 (Legalbox 11, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Feb. 1989 (Legalbox 11, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Mar. - Dec. 1989 (Legalbox 11, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Jan. - May 1990 (Legalbox 11, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Dec. 1990 (Legalbox 11, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Oct. - Dec. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Jan. - May 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, Feb. - Apr. 1991 (Legalbox 11, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Nov. 1991 (Legalbox 11, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, Feb. - Nov. 1992 (Legalbox 12, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, Sept. 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Nov. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, Aug. - Sept. 1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, Oct. - Dec. 1995 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Jan. - Nov. 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, Sept. - Nov. 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, undated (Legalbox 12, Folder 2)
- General Records, 1889-1999; 1889 1999
  The General Records series contains Athletics records that do not relate specifically to a single sport; these records either contain information about several sports, or provide general information about the Athletics programs at NC State, as well as the facilities where sporting events were held. This series is arranged roughly chronologically by academic year.
  - Athletics history, 1889-1966 (Legalbox 260, Folder 9)
  - Raleigh High School Football and Baseball clippings, circa 1910s (Box 262, Folder 22)
  - Student athletic tickets, 1931-1941 (Box 262, Folder 23)
  - "'Hunk' Anderson Welcomed at NC State" college brochure, 1933-1934 (Box 262, Folder 24)
  - Intercollegiate Athletic Program brochure, 1936 (Box 262, Folder 25)
  - Season review, 1946-1947 (Legalbox 260, Folder 10)
  - Disbursements, by sport, 1 Jul. - 24 Nov. 1948 (Box 262, Folder 26)
  - Winter Sports media guide, 1948-1949 (Box 262, Folder 27)
  - Athletics report, 1950-1951 (Legalbox 260, Folder 11)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1952 (Box 262, Folder 28)
  - Fall Quarter Sports schedule, 1952 (Box 262, Folder 29)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1953 (Box 262, Folder 30)
  - Final Sports report, 1954-1955 (Legalbox 260, Folder 12)
  - Athletics Report, 1955-1956 (Box 262, Folder 32)
  - Home activities in Athletics at Reynolds Coliseum, 1956-1957 (Box 262, Folder 33)
  - Sports schedules, 1957-1958 (Box 262, Folder 34)
  - Spring Athletics Schedule, 1959 (Box 262, Folder 35)
  - "Stadium Development" brochure, circa 1960s (Box 262, Folder 36)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1960 (Box 262, Folder 37)
  - Atlantic Coast Sports Writers Association Membership, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 260, Folder 13)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1960 (Box 262, Folder 38)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1960-1961 (Box 262, Folder 39)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1961 (Box 262, Folder 40)
  - Athletics Review, 1961-1962 (Box 262, Folder 41)
  - Intercollegiate schedule, 1961-1962 (Box 262, Folder 42)
  - Fall Sports, 1961 (Legalbox 260, Folder 14)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1961-1962 (Box 262, Folder 43)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1962 (Box 262, Folder 44)
  - Letter winners, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 260, Folder 15)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1962 (Box 262, Folder 45)
  - Miss Sweden visit to Athletics, Nov. 1962 (Box 262, Folder 46)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 260, Folder 16)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1963 (Legalbox 260, Folder 17)
  - Athletics review, 1963-1964 (Box 262, Folder 47)
  - Letter winners, 1963-1964 (Legalbox 260, Folder 18)
  - Fall Sports, 1963 (Box 262, Folder 48)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1963-1964 (Legalbox 260, Folder 19)
  - Helms Athletic Foundation, 1963-1965 (Box 262, Folder 49)
  - Athletics Review, 1964-1965 (Legalbox 260, Folder 20)
  - Civic Club Night, 14 Sept. 1964 (Box 262, Folder 50)
  - Letter to Monogram Club, 25 Sept. 1964 (Box 262, Folder 51)
  - University name change, 1964-1965 (Box 262, Folder 52)
  - Fall Sports, 1964 (Legalbox 260, Folder 21)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1964-1965 (Box 262, Folder 53)
  - Spring Sports, 1965 (Legalbox 260, Folder 22)
  - Reynolds Coliseum Calendar of Events, 1965-1966 (Box 262, Folder 54)
  - Fall Sports, 1965 (Legalbox 260, Folder 24)
  - Winter Sports, 1965-1966 (Legalbox 260, Folder 25)
  - Spring Sports, 1966 (Box 262, Folder 55)
  - Athletics review, 1966-1967 (Legalbox 260, Folder 26)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1966 (Box 262, Folder 56)
  - Dedication of Carter Stadium and A. E. Finley Fieldhouse, 8 Oct. 1966 (Box 262, Folder 57)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1967 (Legalbox 260, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with the Fayettville Observer, May 1967 (Box 262, Folder 58)
  - Reynolds Coliseum calendar of events, 1967-1968 (Legalbox 265, Folder 1)
  - WPTF coverage for Football and Men's Basketball, 1967-1973 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1967 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1967-1968 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Spring Sports, 1968 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Athletics review, 1968-1969 (Legalbox 265, Folder 2)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1968 (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Football-Basketball schedule, 1968-1969 (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Winter Sports, 1968-1969 (Legalbox 265, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds Coliseum Calendar of Events, 1969 (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Spring Sports, 1969 (Legalbox 265, Folder 4)
  - Roy Clogston-Paul Derr Testimonial Dinner, 8 May 1969 (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Golf-Tennis-Track Championships: program, 8-10 May 1969 (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Spring Sports Jamboree, 8-10 May 1969 (Legalbox 265, Folder 5)
  - Athletics Review, 1969-1970 (Box 263, Folder 10)
  - Athletics review, 1969-1970 (Legalbox 265, Folder 6)
  - National Sportswriters and Sportscasters Banquet, 1969-1972 (Box 263, Folder 11)
  - Outstanding College Athletes of America award, 1969-1971 (Box 263, Folder 12)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1969-1970 (Box 263, Folder 13)
  - Spring Sports, 1970 (Legalbox 265, Folder 7)
  - Athletics review, 1970-1971 (Legalbox 265, Folder 8)
  - Reynolds Coliseum Calendar of Events, 1970-1971 (Box 263, Folder 14)
  - Football and Men's Basketball schedule, 1970-1971 (Box 263, Folder 15)
  - Fall Sports, 1970 (Legalbox 265, Folder 9)
  - Winter Sports, 1970-1971 (Legalbox 265, Folder 10)
  - Spring Sports, 1971 (Legalbox 265, Folder 11)
  - Athletics Review, 1971-1972 (Box 263, Folder 16)
  - Football and Men's Basketball schedule, 1971-1972 (Box 263, Folder 17)
  - Fall Sports, 1971 (Box 263, Folder 18)
  - Winter Sports, 1971-1972 (Legalbox 265, Folder 12)
  - Spring Sports, 1972 (Legalbox 265, Folder 13)
  - Athletics Review, 1972-1973 (Box 263, Folder 19)
  - Clippings holder, 1972 (Box 263, Folder 20)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1972 (Box 263, Folder 21)
  - "This is Carolina Blue: Look at it closely..." patch, Sept. 1972 (Box 263, Folder 22)
  - Winter Sports, 1972-1973 (Box 263, Folder 23)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1973 (Box 263, Folder 24)
  - Athletics Review, 1973-1974 (Box 263, Folder 25)
  - "Coach and Athlete", 1973-1975 (Box 263, Folder 26)
  - Fall Sports, 1973 (Box 263, Folder 27)
  - Winter Sports, 1973-1974 (Box 263, Folder 28)
  - Spring Sports, 1974 (Box 263, Folder 29)
  - Winter Sports, 1974-1975 (Box 263, Folder 30)
  - Spring Sports, 1975 (Box 263, Folder 31)
  - Fall Sports, 1975 (Box 263, Folder 32)
  - Winter Sports, 1975-1976 (Box 263, Folder 33)
  - Spring Sports, 1976 (Box 263, Folder 34)
  - Sports Calendar, 1976-1977 (Box 263, Folder 35)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1976 (Box 263, Folder 36)
  - Wolfpack Sports Network: Sponsor's Day, 25 Sept. 1976 (Box 263, Folder 37)
  - Technician Wolfpack Basketball preview, 1976-1977 (Legalbox 265, Folder 14)
  - Winter Sports, 1976-1977 (Box 263, Folder 38)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1977 (Box 263, Folder 39)
  - "Beyond the Locker Room: Athletic Administration and Fund Raising", 30-31 May 1977 (Box 263, Folder 40)
  - Technician Wolfpack Basketball preview, 1977-1978 (Box 263, Folder 41)
  - Wolfpack Sports Network: general information, 1977-1978 (Box 263, Folder 42)
  - Wolfpack Sports Network: income reports, 1977-1978 (Box 263, Folder 43)
  - "Women's Athletics" booklet, 1977-1978 (Box 263, Folder 44)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1977 (Box 263, Folder 45)
  - Winter Sports, 1977-1978 (Box 263, Folder 46)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1978 (Box 263, Folder 47)
  - Technician State Basketball preview, 1978-1979 (Box 263, Folder 48)
  - Wolfpack Sports Network: Budweiser Contract, 1978-1979 (Box 263, Folder 49)
  - Wolfpack Sports Network: general information, 1978-1979 (Box 263, Folder 50)
  - Wolfpack Sports Network: station contracts, 1978-1979 (Box 263, Folder 51)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1978-1979 (Box 263, Folder 52)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1979 (Box 263, Folder 53)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1979 (Box 263, Folder 54)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 263, Folder 55)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1980 (Box 263, Folder 56)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1980 (Box 263, Folder 57)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 263, Folder 58)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1981 (Box 263, Folder 59)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1981 (Box 263, Folder 60)
  - Reynolds Coliseum rental rates schedule, 5 Oct. 1981 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Junior Striders, 1981-1982 (Box 266, Folder 32)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1981-1982 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1982 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1982 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1983 (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1983-1984 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - "Academic factors" supplement to recruiting letter, 1984 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - NC State University All-Sports Banquet (6th Annual), 24 Apr. 1984 (Box 264, Folder 9)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1984 (Box 264, Folder 10)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1984 (Box 264, Folder 11)
  - Winter Sports, 1984-1985 (Box 264, Folder 12)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1985 (Box 264, Folder 13)
  - NC State University All-Sports Banquet (7th Annual), 23 Apr. 1985 (Box 264, Folder 14)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1985 (Box 264, Folder 15)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1986 (Box 264, Folder 16)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1986 (Box 264, Folder 17)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1986-1987 (Box 264, Folder 18)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 19)
  - All-Sports Banquet (9th Annual), 21 Apr. 1987 (Box 264, Folder 20)
  - Fall Sports schedule, 1988 (Box 264, Folder 21)
  - Student Athlete Handbook, Jan. 1989 (Box 264, Folder 22)
  - Spring Sports schedule, 1989 (Box 264, Folder 23)
  - All-Sports Banquet (11th Annual), 17 Apr. 1989 (Box 264, Folder 24)
  - Student Athlete Handbook, Aug. 1989 (Box 266, Folder 33)
  - Director of Athletics Search Committee letter, 24 Oct. 1989 (Box 264, Folder 25)
  - Winter Sports schedule, 1989-1990 (Box 264, Folder 26)
  - Addam's mail-order apparel catalog, 1990 (Box 264, Folder 27)